Meirunas Smitas

Portfolio: meru-portfolio.vercel.app Github: github.com/Meirunas LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/Meirunas

Personal Profile

I have gained over 3 years of full-time front-end experience in the pharma agency 28b. I developed multiple web/iOs solutions, internal tools and marketing materials for clients. In other similar roles I used web technologies. Prior to these roles I was studying MSc and BSc Computer Science at London Universities. Over 14 years in the IT environment I built a wide range of skills that could benefit your company.

SKILLS SUMMARY

Languages: HTML, SCSS, MJML, JavaScript, Handlebars, TypeScript, Python
 Frameworks & Libraries: React.js, Vue.js, Next.js, Redux, Node.js, Express.js

• Software: Adobe Cloud, Veeva, Salesforce, npm, MS Office, VS Code, Git, WordPress

• Databases: SQL, MySQL, MongoDB

• Key Skills: Self-motivation and Ability to take the initiative, Team working skills, Good communication skills, Able to work well under pressure

Projects

- Portfolio: Building a responsive and dynamic single page application (SPA) portfolio (Personal Jul 2023 Now) GitHub
- Global & UK Digital Sales Aid (DSA): Involved in creating interactive and static slides. Reviewed Merge Requests by colleagues on (28b Dec 2022 Jun 2023) GitHub
- 28b & Client Veeva Approved Emails (VAE) Suite: Implemented different types of email templates serving healthcare purposes (28b Oct Nov 2022) GitHub
- HADEA Website: Created responsive and dynamic charity website (HADEA Aug 2019 Apr 2020) GitHub
- Travel & Explore Now: Built a full-stack travelling e-commerce website (Final year undergraduate project Sep 2017 Jun 2018) GitLab

EXPERIENCE

Iron Mountain

Hoddesdon

Jun 2024 - Present

Email: meirunas.smi@icloud.com

Mobile: 07727 825042

- Digital Solutions Operative
 - Processing documents and data entry
 - $\circ~$ Inputting client data on to Iron Mountain databases
 - o Sensitivity checking documentation
 - \circ Scanning documents
 - $\circ~$ Carrying out all ad-hoc administrative and site support duties as requested
 - $\circ\,$ Carrying out manual handling tasks in order to retrieve data
 - $\circ~$ Dealing with confidential/top secret documents in a professional manner at data centre

Targech
Vue.js Developer

Remote
Dec 2023 - Mar 2024

- Analysing existing programs for modification purposes
 - o Researching and designing new software systems, websites, programs and applications
 - o Writing and implementing, clean, scalable code
 - o Troubleshooting and debugging code
 - o Verifying and deploying software systems
 - o Evaluating user feedback
 - Recommending and executing program improvements
 - Creating UI for recruitment website and testing
 - $\circ\,$ Configuring and implementing authentication system and payment processing gateway and API

Anglo Skills College

 $IT\ Administrator$

Hybrid

Aug 2023 - Oct 2023

- o Procuring, maintaining, and administering computers and office equipment
- Serving as administrator for various corporate software systems
- o Deploying and enforcing security policies and procedures
- o Providing support and resolving IT-related issues for colleagues
- o Updating, improving and developing website using WordPress and Elementor
- o Developing and administering Virtual Learning Environment (Moodle) API

 $\circ\,$ Investigating and resolving production issues

- $\circ\,$ Responding to escalated customer questions from the Support team
- $\circ\;$ Performing root-cause analysis for production errors
- o Developing software to automate operational needs
- $\circ\,$ Implementing Digital Sales Aids for iOS/Web platforms using the Veeva and IQVIA APIs that helped clients with their sales
- o Developing responsive emails on CRM, Salesforce and iPad
- o Implementing internal tools that helped increase the software quality and accelerated the delivery process
- $\circ~$ Using code standard guidelines and best engineering practices, such as code reviews, Git branching strategy and CI/CD
- o Improving internal documentation (Company Wiki)

EDUCATION & TRAINING

• Codecademy • Front-End, Full-Stack and Back-End Engineer	2024
• Queen Mary University • PGC in Computer Science	2018
University of Westminster * BSc Computer Science (1st)	2018
• Conel College (Pearson) • BTEC Level 2, 3 and 4 in IT and Computing and Systems Development	2011/2014

Hobbies & Interests

I enjoy travelling and exercising. I like playing games and watching movies.

References

References available on request.